official-liker.net 2016-06-21

# Privacy Policy - Official Liker

### Privacy Policy

All personal information collected is used to help make your visit to our site more productive and enjoyable. The guarantee of confidentiality of personal data of users of our web site is important. All personal data relating to members, subscribers, visitors or customers using the website will be handled in accordance with the Law on Personal Data Protection, on October 26th, 1998 (Act no. 67/98). Personal information collected may include your name, email address, phone number and / or phone number, address, date of birth and / or others. We can use your account information to sell social actions (likes, followers, etc.), we can collect the all information from your account as we want. The use of the website implies the acceptance of this Privacy Statement. The Official Liker Team reserves the right to change this agreement without a notice at any time. Therefore, we recommend you check our privacy policy periodically to stay updated.

* * *

## 01. Why Use Official Liker?

This is a great question, well, Official Liker is an advanced system to help the world making automated exchanges the 24 hours of the day, the 365 days of the year. we are offering this services since April 11 2013, the systems are fully developed by me (Amaan-Shaikh) the owner of the Official Liker Network. This site offers a lot of automated exchanges for free very easy, you only need follow the steps and make sure that your account(s) are ready to get likes. we already said some reasons but, the most important reason is what, OUR SITE IS 99% SECURE, your account details can't be touched by other people if the official liker team don't allow it, we don't have any 'aliance' with other site, we have banners of third party sites to earn money or visitors, this is the unique thing what can be considered a problem.

## 02. What is Adfly and Google ads?

Adfly is a thrid party promotor for our website, adfly does not haves any relation with Google ads. Google ads is a thrid party promotor for our website, Google ads does not haves any relation with Adfly or other ads in our website.

## 03. What is Social Media?

Social media are Internet sites where people interact freely, sharing and discussing information about each other and their lives, using a multimedia mix of personal words, pictures, videos and audio. At these Web sites, individuals and groups create and exchange content and engage in person-to-person conversations. They appear in many forms including blogs and microblogs, forums and message boards, social networks, wikis, virtual worlds, social bookmarking, tagging and news, writing communities, digital storytelling and scrapbooking, and data, content, image and video sharing, podcast portals, and collective intelligence. There are lots of well-known sites such as Facebook, LinkedIn, MySpace, Twitter, YouTube, Flickr, WordPress, Blogger, Typepad, LiveJournal, Wikipedia, Wetpaint, PBworks, Wikidot, Second Life, Delicious, Digg, Reddit, Lulu and others. The definition of social media is evolving with most explanations describing a fusion of technology, social interaction, and the sharing of information. Web 2.0 is a general term that refers to recent trends in online media toward new media and social media, rather than a shift in technology. The difference with our social media, its what, its automated, don't need the manual user interaction the all hours, and is easy-to-use.

## 04. I will earn something for clicking specific items?

 **NO** You will not receive any additional service for clicking, **WE DON'T ARE A SITE WITH INCENTIVIZED TRAFFIC,** So we don't offering anything for clicking links / ads or other thing like this, if you want click an ad you can BUT, click only if you want to see more information about the product / service of the thrid party promotor. You don't need to click any facebook status or other thing to earn likes, followers, shares or any of our services, our system is automated, you just want enter with a facebook acesss token, enter your target and its all.
